Finding Aid for Gerald R. Ford School of Public Policy (University of Michigan) Publications 1923-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Gerald R. Ford School of Public Policy (University of Michigan) Publications
1923-2006
University of Michigan. Gerald R. Ford School of Public Policy.
6.2 linear feet
1 bundles
Includes brochures, manuals, proceedings, programs, and reports. Also contains bulletins or course catalogs from the School of Public Policy, the Institute of Public Policy Studies, the Institute of Public Administration, and the Institute of Public and Social Administration. Contains 1967 and 1968 W. S. Woytinsky lectures and the newsletters Newsletter: Institute of Public Administration, IPPS Newsletter and the School of Public Policy Newsletter. Also includes Bureau of Government bulletins, pamphlets, and reports and the newsletter The Staebler Caucus published by the Neil Staebler Political Education Fund. Also contains the Newsletter to Graduates published by the Michigan chapter of the American Society for Public Administration.
97132 Bimu 2
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
Publications are received periodically from the unit (donor no. 2951 ).
Periodic additions to the records expected.
The School of Public Policy publications are open for research.
See the historical sketch in the finding aid for Gerald R. Ford School of Public Policy Records.
The Publications of the Gerald R. Ford School of Public Policy (6.2 linear feet) are divided into three subseries: Unit Publications, Sub-Unit Publications, and Student Publications. Some publications (or their successors) may no longer be available in print but are available on the school s website.
Subjects:
University of Michigan. School of Public Policy.; University of Michigan. Institute of Public Policy Studies.; University of Michigan. Institute of Public Administration.; University of Michigan. Institute of Public and Social Administration.; University of Michigan. Bureau of Government.
Publications:
Staebler caucus.
Contributors:
University of Michigan. Institute of Public Policy Studies.; University of Michigan. Institute of Public Administration.; University of Michigan. Institute of Public and Social Administration.; University of Michigan. Bureau of Government.; Neil Staebler Political Education Fund.; American Society for Public Administration. Michigan Chapter.
Publications:
Staebler caucus.
Genre/Form:
Brochures.; Lectures.; Manuals.; Catalogs, College.; Newsletters.; Proceedings.; Programs.; Reports.; Student publications.
- Unit Publications
  The Unit Publications (2.5 linear feet) include brochures, manuals, magazines, newsletters, posters, proceedings, programs, and reports. All publications of the Institute of Public Administration, Institute of Public Policy Studies, and the School of Public Policy are in this series. The bulletins or course catalogs are arranged chronologically from 1936 through 1994. There are also printed editions of the first two W. S. Woytinsky Lectures from 1967 and 1968. These will be found under the heading "Lectures".
  The newsletters of the School of Public Policy and its predecessors are arranged alphabetically by title. The Newsletter: Institute of Public Administration was published from 1956 to 1958 and 1960 to 1965. This publication focused on the activities of the faculty and the students, both professional and personal. Unit Publications also include issues of the IPPS Newsletter from the years 1978 to 1986 and from 1994 to 1995. It describes activities within the Institute of Public Policy Studies, as well as news about the faculty, staff, students, and alumni. When the institute became the School of Public Policy in 1995 the name of the newsletter changed to the School of Public Policy Newsletter.
  - Brochures
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration Institute of Public Administration, 1964 (Box 1)
    - General, 1986; undated (Box 1)
    - Gerald R. Ford School of Public Policy Celebration and Naming Ceremony, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Joan and Sanford Weill Hall dedication, 2006 (Box 1)
    - Institute of Public Policy Studies, circa 1981 (Box 1)
    - Public Leadership: Governing for the 21st Century, undated (Box 1)
    - Site dedication ceremony, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Bulletins (Degree program requirement)
    - The Institute of Public and Social Administration Announcement, 1936-1938; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - The Institute of Public and Social Administration Curriculum in Public Administration Announcement, 1939-1940 (Box 1)
    - Graduate Curriculum in Social Work Announcement, 1936-1937 (Box 1)
    - Curriculum in Social Work Announcement Summer Session, 1938 (Box 1)
    - Curriculum in Social Work Announcement
      - 1939-1943, 6 volumes (Box 1)
      - 1944-1946 (Box 1)
    - Institute of Public Administration Announcement
      - 1946-1954, 4 folders (Box 1)
      - 1958-1962, 2 folders (Box 1)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 1)
    - Institute of Public Policy Studies: Program in Public Administration (Box 1)
      - 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Institute of Public Policy Studies
      - 1972-1980, 4 folders (Box 1)
      - 1984-1989, 3 folders (Box 1)
      - 1989-1994, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - School of Public Policy, 1995-2001 (Box 5)
    - Gerald R. School of Public Policy
      - 2001/02 (Box 5)
      - 2002/03 (Box 5)
      - Supplement, 2003/04 (Box 5)
      - 2004/06 (Box 5)
    - Ph.D. Joint Programs, circa, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Directories
    - Alumni directory, 1999
  - Discussion Papers
    - The Kidney Problem: An Exercise in the Clarification of Policy Goals by Ronald D. Brunner
      - Case Materials, 1977 (Box 1)
      - Instructor's Guide and Bibliography, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Lectures
    - Citigroup Lecture, 2002; 2011 (Box 1)
    - W. S. Woytinsky Lecture
      - No. 1, Human Capital and the Personal Distribution of Income: An Analytical Approach by Gary S. Becker, 1967 (Box 1)
      - No. 2, Guideposts for Wages and Prices: Criteria and Consistency by Edward F. Dension, 1968 (Box 1)
      - No. 4, Individual Behavior, Economic Analysis and Public Policy, by James N. Morgan, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Lectures and Presentations
    - Event Flyers, 2011-2012 (Box 5)
    - Posters and Flyers Inventory, 2002-2012 (Box 5)
    - Policy Talks, 2012-2013 (Box 5)
    - Posters and Flyers, 2002-2010 (Bundle 1)
  - Manuals
    - IPPS Guide to Summer Internships and Summer Employment, undated (Box 1)
    - Study Kit on Michigan Local Government, 1954; 1958; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Magazine
    - State & Hill
      supersedes SPP Newsletter
      - 2009-2010 (Box 6)
      - 2012-2013 (Box 6)
  - Newsletters
    - IPPS Newsletter, and1994-1995, 1978-1986 (Box 6)
      [Continues as School of Public Policy Newsletter]
      - 1978-1983 (Box 6)
      - 1986-1988 (Box 6)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 6)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 6)
    - Newsletter: Institute of Public Administration
      - 1956-1958, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - 1960-1965 (Box 6)
    - School of Public Policy Newsletter
      [Supersedes IPPS Newsletter]
      - 1995-1997, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - 2000-2002 (Box 6)
    - Perspectives, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
      [Supersedes SPP Newsletter]
  - Proceedings
    - Papers in Comparative Public Administration edited by Ferrel Heady and Sybil L. Stokes, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Proceedings of the First Annual Workshop on US-Canadian Relations, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Programs
    - IPPS/IPA Anniversary Celebration, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Management Clinic, 1949-1950 (Box 1)
  - Reports
    - A Case Study in Cost Effectiveness: Proposed Expansion of University of Michigan Athletic Facilities by George M. Galloway, undated (Box 1)
    - The Curriculum in Social Work: A Report of the First Five Years, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Demographic Information About IPPS Students, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Financial Analysis of Current Operations of Colleges and Universities: Cooperative Research Project No. 1853, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Report of the Advisory Council on Public Administration to the Executive Committee of the Institute of Public Administration, [1967] (Box 1)
    - State/Provincial Administrators in Michigan, Missouri, and Ontario: A Report to Respondents, by Catherine Pastathopoulos, David A. Leuthold, and Robert S. Friedman, 1969 (Box 1)
    - University Centers for the Study of Public Policy: Organizational Viability by John P. Crecine, undated (Box 1)
- Sub-Unit Publications
  The Sub-Unit Publications series (3.3 linear feet) includes bulletins, pamphlets, and reports from the Bureau of Government. The bulletins and pamphlets focus on various aspects of Michigan government such as taxation, the constitution, politics and elections, highway expenditures, and public schools The bulletins are arranged alphabetically by publication series title. These series include the Bulletin, published from 1923 through 1926, the New Series Bulletin, produced from 1932 to 1937, and the Michigan Governmental Digest, issued from 1938 to 1968. Within each series they are arranged numerically. Under the heading "Pamphlets" researchers will find the Michigan Pamphlets series, published from 1939 through 1961. These publications also discuss issues such as government finance, taxation, and government policies, but in a more condensed format than the bulletins. The "Reports" are from a series entitled Papers in Public Administration published from 1948 through 1965. Arranged in a numerical sequence they feature a nearly complete run of the Proceedings of the Annual Short Course for Assessing Officers which was held at the University of Michigan. There are also reports which discuss elections, bureaucracy, taxes, and public opinion polls.
  Included in this series are bulletins or course catalogs, published from 1938 to 1945, by the Institute of Public and Social Administration. These listings describe the courses offerings in the social work program in Detroit. In 1945 the Institute of Public and Social Administration was replaced by the Institute of Public Administration and the Institute of Social Work. These bulletins can also be found in the record group University of Michigan. School of Social Work. Publications.
  This series also includes the newsletter The Staebler Caucus, published from 1988 to 1991, by the Neil Staebler Political Education Fund. There is a single report, no. 3, from the Michigan Populations Studies series. This report entitled College Enrollment Potential in Michigan, 1960-1975 was produced by the Program for Research in Population and Human Ecology in 1961. The Seminar on University Management issued a report entitled Admissions at the University of Michigan During the 1980s and 1990s in 1984.
  - Bureau of Government
    - Bulletins
      - Bulletin
        - No. 1, Per Capita General Property Taxation in Michigan Cities of Over 2,500 Population 1922 by Josephine Hoyt, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - No. 2, Municipal News in Detroit Newspapers by Lida Rideout, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - No. 3, Suggestions for the Preparation of Term Reports on Problems of Municipal Government, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - No. 3, (revised), Suggestions for the Preparation of Term Reports on Problems of Municipal Government, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - No. 4 Zoning Ordinances in Michigan Cities: Use Regulation, 1923 by Lewis M. Gabriel, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - No. 5 The Use of Voting Machines in Michigan, by James K. Pollock, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - No. 6 Home Rule Charters in Michigan by Paul Webbink and W.R. Maddox, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Michigan Governmental Digest, Nos. 1, 3-4, 1946-1949
        - No. 1 An Analysis of the Proposed Sales Tax Amendment by Robert S. Ford, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        - No. 3 Michigan State Constitutional Revision Procedures, by Claude R. Tharp, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        - No. 4 The Little Hoover Commissions by John W. Lederle and Dorothee E. Strauss, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Michigan Governmental Studies, Nos. 1-50, 1938-1968
        - No. 1 The State Administrative Board in Michigan by George C.S. Benson and Edward H. Litchfield, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - No. 2. Taxation of Intangibles in Michigan by Robert S. Ford and William B. Wood, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - No. 3 Voting Behavior: A Case Study by James Kerr Pollock, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - No. 4 A Manual of State Administrative Organization in Michigan, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - No. 5 The Michigan Retail Sales and Use Taxes by Robert S. Ford and E. Fenton Shepard, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - No. 6 The Initiative and Referendum in Michigan by James K. Pollock, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - No. 7 Voting Behavior in a Metropolitan Area by Edward H. Litchfield, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - No. 8 Income as an Index of the Fiscal Capacity of Michigan Counties by Marvin A. Bacon, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - No. 9 Financing Government in Michigan by Robert S. Ford and Albert Waxman, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - No. 10 Michigan Politics in Transition by James K. Pollock and Samuel J. Eldersveld (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - No. 11 The Role of the Governor in Michigan in the Enactment of Appropriations by John A. Perkins, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        - No. 12 Michigan Highway Finance by Robert S. Ford and Marvin A. Bacon, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        - No. 13 The Financing of Public Schools in Michigan by E. Fenton Shepard and William B. Wood, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - No. 14 The Direct Primary in Michigan, 1909-1935 by James K. Pollock (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - No. 15 A Manual of County Administrative Organization in Michigan by Claude R. Tharp, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        - No. 16 Social Security and Related Services in Michigan, Their Administration and Financing by Claude R. Tharp, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        - No. 17 Public Regulation in Action: The Experience of a Michigan Gas Company by Floyd A. Bond, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        - No. 18 A Manual of Township Government in Michigan by Floyd A. Bond, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        - No. 19 The Population of Michigan 1840 to 1960 An Analysis of Growth, Distribution, and Composition by Amos H. Hawley, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        - No. 20 A Manual of State Government in Michigan, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        - No. 21 Governmental Organizations in Metropolitan Areas by Betty Tableman, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 12)
        - No. 22 Manual of City Government in Michigan (Revised Edition) by Claude R. Tharp, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 12)
        - No. 23 Manual of Village Government in Michigan (Revised Edition), by Claude Tharp, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 13)
        - No. 24 Administrative Procedure Legislation in the States by Ferrel Heady, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 13)
        - No. 25 Intrastate Migration in Michigan: 1935-1940 by Amos H. Hawley (Box 2, Folder 14)
        - No. 26 The Special Assessment Today with Emphasis on the Michigan Experience by William O. Winter, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        - No. 27 Career Perspectives in a Bureaucratic Setting by Dwaine Marvick, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 15)
        - No. 28 Methods of State Constitutional Reform by Albert L. Sturm, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 15)
        - No. 29 Michigan State Highway Expenditure Policy by Hubert H. Frisinger, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        - No. 30 Michigan's Recounts for Governor, 1950 and 1952 A Systematic Analysis of Election Error by Samuel J. Eldersveld and Albert A. Applegate, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        - No. 31 The Michigan Department of Administration by Ferrel Heady and Robert H. Pealy, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 17)
        - No. 32 Competitive Pressure and Democratic Consent by Morris Janowitz and Dwaine Marvick, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 17)
        - No. 33 A Comparative Study of Property Tax Administration in Illinois and Michigan by Robert H. Pealy, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 18)
        - No. 34 Political Affiliation in Metropolitan Detroit by Samuel J. Eldersveld, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 18)
        - No. 35 The Michigan Municipal League: An Analysis of Policies and Services by George A. Bell, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 19)
        - No. 36 Public Administration and the Public--Perspectives Toward Government in a Metropolitan Community by Morris Janowitz, Deil Wright, and William Delany, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 19)
        - No. 37 Comprehensive River Basin Planning: The Arkansas-White-Red Basins Inter-Agency Committee Experience by Robert H. Pealy (Box 2, Folder 20)
        - No. 39 The President Makes a Decision: A Study of Dixon-Yates by Jason L. Finkle, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 20)
        - No. 40 The Democratic State Central Committee in Michigan, 1949-1959 The Rise of the New Politics and the New Political Leadership by Robert Lee Sawyer, Jr., 1960 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - No. 41 Personnel Adaptations in the Federal Junior Management Assistant Program by Jonathan Avery Slesinger, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - No. 42 Political Representation in Metropolitan Agencies by Arthur W. Bromage, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 1)
        - No. 43 Constitution-Making in Michigan, 1961-1962 by Albert Lee Sturm, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 1)
        - No. 44 The Michigan Constitutional Convention and Administrative Organization: A Case Study in the Politics of Constitution-Making by Robert S. Friedman, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 1)
        - No. 45 State Budgeting for Higher Education: The Use of Formulas and Cost Analysis by James L. Miller, Jr., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 2)
        - No. 46 Organization for Comprehensive River Basin Planning: The Texas and Southeast Experiences by Robert H. Pealy, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 2)
        - No. 47 Income Distribution and the Federal Income Tax by Benjamin A. Okner, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
        - No. 48 Normative Evaluation of a Public Health Program by William B. Neenan, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
        - No. 49 Essays in State and Local Finance, edited by Harvey E. Brazer, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
        - No. 50 Implementing a New Constitution: The Michigan Experience, by Albert L. Sturm and Margaret Whitaker, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - New Series Bulletin, No. 1-8, 1932-1937
        - No. 1 Tentative Conclusions with respect to the position of the Township in the Governmental Scheme, by Arthur W. Bromage, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 5)
        - No. 2 County Election Costs in Michigan, by James Kerr Pollock, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 5)
        - No. 3 Civil Service in the States: A Selected and Annotated Bibliography on the Laws, Regulations and Practices in the State Governments of the United States, by Ione M. Dority, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 5)
        - No. 4 Recent Developments in the Michigan Tax Situation, by Robert S. Ford, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - No. 5 Administrative Organization of State Government in Michigan, 1921-1936, by Harold M. Dorr (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - No. 5 (Supplement) Administrative Reorganizations, 1936-1937, by Harold M. Dorr, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - No. 6 The Retail Sales Tax in Michigan, by Robert S. Ford, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - No. 7 Permanent Registration of Voters in Michigan: An Appraisal, by James K. Pollock, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 7)
        - No. 8 Realty Tax Delinquency in Michigan, by Robert S. Ford, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Pamphlets
      - Michigan Pamphlets, Nos. 1-30, 1939-1961
        - No. 1 Taxing Intangibles--The Problem and Methods, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 8)
        - No. 2 Financing Michigan's Government: 1930-1938, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 8)
        - No. 3 Property Tax Administration, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 8)
        - No. 4 Tax and Salvage Sales, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 8)
        - No. 5 Trends in Highway Finance, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - No. 6 State Tax Administration, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - No. 7 Local Government in Cheboygan County, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - No. 8 Direct Government in Michigan, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - No. 9 Local Government in Branch County, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - No. 10 Financing National Defense, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - No. 11 Units of Government in Michigan, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - No. 12 Retail Sales Taxation in Michigan, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - No. 13 Federal Expenditures in Michigan, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - No. 14 Local Government in Genesee County, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - No. 15 State Supervision of Local Borrowing, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 11)
        - No. 16 An Experiment in Community Improvement, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 11)
        - No. 17 Administration and Financing of Public Relief, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 11)
        - No. 18 State Aid in Michigan, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 11)
        - No. 19 Reorganization of Michigan's County Government, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 12)
        - No. 20 State Aid and Local Finance in Selected Michigan Counties, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 12)
        - No. 21 Paying for Public Schools in Michigan, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 13)
        - No. 22 Property Tax Administration in Michigan, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 13)
        - No. 23 Michigan Cities and Villages: Organization and Administration, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 13)
        - No. 24 Public Services to Children in Michigan: A Study of Basic Structure, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 14)
        - No. 25 Press Relations for Local Officials by James C. MacDonald, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 15)
        - No. 26 The Urban Fringe Problem: Solutions Under Michigan Law by Ralph T. Jans, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 15)
        - No. 27 The Voter and the Michigan Constitution in 1958 edited by Robert H. Pealy (Box 3, Folder 15)
        - No. 28 A Program for Federal Tax Revision by Harvey E. Brazer, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 16)
        - No. 29 The Voter and the Michigan Constitution edited by Robert H. Pealy, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 16)
        - No. 30 Taxation in Michigan: An Appraisal by Harvey E. Brazer, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Reports
      - Papers in Public Administration
        - No. 1, 1948 (Box 3)
          (includes nine papers)
        - No. 2, 1948 (Box 3)
          (includes 8 articles by four authors)
        - No. 3 Proceedings of the Third Annual Short Course for Municipal Assessing Officers..., 1949 (Box 3)
        - No. 4 Proceedings of the Fourth Annual Short Course for Municipal Assessing Officers..., 1950 (Box 3)
        - No. 5 Analysis of Annexation in Michigan Together with a Comparison of Annexation in Other States by Robert E. Fryer, 1951 (Box 3)
        - No. 6 A Series of Graduate Students' Reports, 1950 (Box 3)
        - No. 7 Proceedings of the Fifth Annual Short Course for Municipal Assessing Officers..., 1951 (Box 3)
        - No. 8 Proceedings of the Sixth Annual Short Course for Assessing Officers..., 1952 (Box 3)
        - No. 9 Proceedings of the Seventh Annual Short Course for Assessing Officers..., 1953 (Box 3)
        - No. 10 Papers on Municipal Nonproperty Taxes in Michigan by Arthur M. Wisehart, 1954 (Box 3)
        - No. 11 Proceedings of the Eighth Annual Short Course for Assessing Officers..., 1954 (Box 3)
        - No. 12 Three Aspects of Records Management: A Transcript of Remarks edited by Theodore H. Drews, 1955 (Box 3)
        - No. 13 Charter Provisions for Personnel Administration in Michigan Cities by Henry Spiegelblatt, 1955 (Box 3)
        - No. 16 Payments in Lieu of Taxes on Public Lands Under the Jurisdiction of the Michigan Department of Conservation by John H. Eichstedt, 1956 (Box 3)
        - No. 17 The Role of Public Opinion Polls in the Study of Political Parties by John P. White, 1956 (Box 3)
        - No. 18 A "Buy-Michigan" Purchasing Policy? by Leiv N. Ryd, 1956 (Box 3)
        - No. 19 Field Organizations of Michigan State Government Departments by Robert H. Pealy and John C. Robertson, 1956 (Box 3)
        - No. 20 Proceedings of the Tenth Annual Short Course for Assessing Officers..., 1956 (Box 3)
        - No. 21 Proceedings of the Eleventh Annual Short Course for Assessing Officers..., 1957 (Box 4)